MILKA LILLQVIST

CONTACT ME

(+358) 0409658471

milka.lillqvist@gmail.com

90900 Kiiminki, Oulu Rengastie 14

SKILLS

Responsible

Hard-working

Spontaneous

stress tolerance

Problem-solving

EDUCATION

Software Developer

OSAO Kaukovainio

2021-202x

Currently a student at OSAO.

LANGUAGE

Finnish

English



PROFILE

I am a 18-year-old, curious, and eager-to-learn individual hailing from the Oulu region. I possess a sense of humor and a calm demeanor, but I am also responsible and reliable. As an employee, I am punctual and diligent. I'm not afraid to seek assistance when things don't progress as expected or if I make a mistake. I believe I have strong English language skills, which lets me connect with individuals whose native language isn't Finnish. Moreover, helping others brings joy to my life. I look forward to the opportunities to contribute my skills in a supportive environment.

EXPERIENCE

Helper in kindergarten

Päiväkoti Mansikkamaa, Kiiminki

3.7.2023 - 14.7.2023

- I helped to look after 1-5 year old children.
- I played and kept them company.
- · After the children went to sleep, I cleaned up the rooms thoroughly.

Café helper

Hölökkyvä Hölli, Oulun tori

1.8.2022 - 28.8.2022

- Mainly, I either washed dishes or collected dishes around the courtyard café.
- I collected garbage, cleaned the tables, washed the table legs, swept the yard, washed laundry, I kept the tables and chairs in order, and I took care of the flowers in the yard.
- Helped lots of customers the best I could.

Job practice at electronics store

Power, Limingantulli

2.5.2022 - 17.6.2022

- Helped customers and salespersons on various of tasks.
- Installed few Windows to laptops under guidance.
- · Kept the shelves organized and public spaces tidy.
- Installed lots of electronic price tags to shelves.

Work experience in spare parts store (TET)

Tavo. Oulu

26.10.2020 - 30.10.2020

- Changed the price tags of all products needing them.
- Unloaded few orders and put them to shelves.
- Helped the staff with other simple tasks.

Work experience in school canteen (TET)

Jokirannan koulu, Kiiminki

2018

• I thoroughly washed the dishes and arranged the dishes to their right places.